Jai Hyun Park

☑ jaihyunp@cryptolab.co.kr

https://jaihyunp.github.io

OVERVIEW

I am a full-time researcher at CryptoLab in Lyon, France. I obtained my Ph.D. in Mathematical Sciences at Seoul National University, advised by Prof. Jung Hee Cheon. I am interested in a broad range of topics in cryptography, from theory to practice. Currently, my research focus is on fully homomorphic encryption and its applications.

EMPLOYMENT

CryptoLab, Lyon, France

Junior Researcher

Sep 2024 - Present

EDUCATION

Seoul National University, Seoul, Republic of Korea

• Ph.D. in Mathematical Sciences

Mar 2020 - Aug 2024

- Advisor: Prof. Jung Hee Cheon
- Focus: Cryptography (Homomorphic Encryption)
- Thesis: Matrix Multiplication on Encrypted Data
- B.S. in Mathematical Sciences

Mar 2013 – Feb 2020

PUBLICATIONS

In the list below, the symbol = indicates papers with alphabetically-ordered authors. The corresponding author is indicated by a dagger (†) for the journal papers.

CONFERENCES

- = [C05] Youngjin Bae, Jung Hee Cheon, Guillaume Hanrot, Jai Hyun Park, Damien Stehlé, "Plaintext-Ciphertext Matrix Multiplication and FHE Bootstrapping: Fast and Fused," *Annual International Cryptology Conference (CRYPTO 2024)*
- = [C04] Rashmi Agrawal, Jung Ho Ahn, Flavio Bergamaschi, Ro Cammarota, Jung Hee Cheon, Fillipe D. M. de Souza, Huijing Gong, Minsik Kang, Duhyeong Kim, Jongmin Kim, Hubert de Lassus, Jai Hyun Park, Michael Steiner, Wen Wang, "High-precision RNS-CKKS on fixed but smaller word-size architectures: theory and application," 11th Workshop on Encrypted Computing & Applied Homomorphic Cryptography (WAHC 2023)
- = [C03] Youngjin Bae, Jung Hee Cheon, Jaehyung Kim, <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>, Damien Stehlé, "HERMES: Efficient Ring Packing using MLWE Ciphertexts and Application to Transciphering," *Annual International Cryptology Conference (CRYPTO 2023)*
 - Best Award, Korea Cryptography Contest 2023
 - [C02] Garam Lee*, Minsoo Kim*, Jai Hyun Park*, Seung-won Hwang, Jung Hee Cheon, "Privacy-Preserving Text Classification on BERT Embeddings with Homomorphic Encryption," Annual Conference of the North American Chapter of the Association for Computational Linguistics (NAACL 2022, short)
 - The authors with the asterisk symbol (*) contributed equally.
- = [C01] Jung Hee Cheon, Duhyeong Kim, Jai Hyun Park, "Towards a Practical Cluster Analysis over Encrypted Data," *International Conference on Selected Areas in Cryptography (SAC 2019)*

JOURNALS

- = [J05] Jung Hee Cheon, Wootae Kim, Jai Hyun Park[†], "Efficient Homomorphic Evaluation on Large Intervals," *IEEE Transactions on Information Forensics and Security*, 2022
 - Excellence Award, Korea Cryptography Contest 2020
 - [J04] <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>, Jung Hee Cheon, Dongwoo Kim[†], "Efficient verifiable computation over quotient polynomial rings," *International Journal of Information Security*, 2022
 - [J03] Seungwan Hong[†], Jai Hyun Park, Wonhee Cho, Hyeongmin Choe, Jung Hee Cheon, "Secure tumor classification by shallow neural network using homomorphic encryption," *BMC Genomics*, 2022
 - First Place Prize, iDASH Genomic Data Privacy and Security Protection Competition 2020

- [J02] Heehoon Kim[†], Seunghyo Kang, <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>, Hyunho Ha, Donghoon Lim, "Noise Removal using Support Vector Regression in Noisy Document Images," *The Korean Journal of Applied Statistics*, 2012
 - Bronze Award, 18th Samsung Humantech Paper Award for High Schools
- [J01] Heehoon Kim[†], Seunghyo Kang, Jai Hyun Park, Hyunho Ha, Jinsoo Lim, Donghoon Lim, "Robust Image Fusion Using Stationary Wavelet Transform," The Korean Journal of Applied Statistics, 2011
 - Silver Award, 18th Samsung Humantech Paper Award for High Schools

MANUSCRIPTS

- = [M03] Jung Hee Cheon, Hyeongmin Choe, <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>[†], "Tree-based Lookup Table on Batched Encrypted Queries using Homomorphic Encryption," *Available at https://eprint.iacr.org/2024/087*, 2024
- = [M02] Jung Hee Cheon, Keewoo Lee[†], <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>, Yongdong Yeo, "Private Database Query with SIMD-Aware Homomorphic Compression," 2023
 - Special Prize, Korea Cryptography Contest 2023
- = [M01] Jung Hee Cheon, Hyeongmin Choe, Saebyul Jung, Duhyeong Kim, Dah Hoon Lee, Jai Hyun Park, "Arithmetic PCA for Encrypted Data," *Available at https://eprint.iacr.org/2023/1544*, 2023
 - Encouragement Prize, Korea Cryptography Contest 2022

HONORS & AWARDS

 Korea Cryptography Contest National Security Research Institute

Special Prize	Nov 2024
Best Award for [C03]	Oct 2023
Special Prize for [M02]	Oct 2023
Encouragement Prize for [M01]	Oct 2022
Excellence Award for [J05]	Oct 2020

 First Place Prize, iDASH Genomic Data Privacy and Security Protection Competition National Institutes of Health Dec 2020

Track I: Secure multi-label Tumor classification using Homomorphic Encryption

 Award for Excellence in Teaching Seoul National University Sep 2020

For teaching Differential and Integral Calculus

Scholarship

BK 21+ Scholarship
 Ministry of Education of Korea
 \$7,500/year for M.S. and \$12,000/year for Ph.D.

Mar 2020 – Aug 2023

• The Presidential Science Scholarship

Korea Student Aid Foundation

Mar 2013 – Feb 2019

Academic Grant: Tuition + \$5, 000/year for 4 years

Samsung Humantech Paper Award for High School

Samsung Electronics

Silver Award for [J01]

Bronze Award for [J02]

Feb 2012 Feb 2012

 Silver Medal, Korean Mathematical Olympiad Korean Mathematical Society

Sep 2011

TALKS

 Plaintext-Ciphertext Matrix Multiplication and FHE Bootstrapping: Fast and Fused CRYPTO 2024, UC Santa Barbara, USA

Aug 2024

HERMES: Efficient Ring Packing using MLWE Ciphertexts and Application to Transciphering
 CRYPTO 2023, UC Santa Barbara, USA

Aug 2023

 Tree-based Lookup Table on Batched Encrypted Queries using Homomorphic Encryption 2022 KMS Spring Meeting, Virtual

■ Efficient Homomorphic Evaluation on Large Intervals 2020 KMS Fall Meeting, Virtual

Oct 2020

Apr 2022

 Towards a Practical Cluster Analysis over Encrypted Data 2019 KMS Fall Meeting, Hong-ik University, Republic of Korea

Oct 2019

TEACHING

LECTURER

ENS Lyon

Fully Homomorphic Encryption

Fall 2024 (M2)

Co-lecturer with Alain Passelègue and Damien Stehlé.

- Delivered two sessions focusing on homomorphic linear algebra.

TEACHING ASSISTANT

Seoul National University

• Computational Number Theory

Spring 2023

· Number Theory

Spring 2021

• Differential and Integral Calculus

Spring 2020 – Spring 2023

PATENTS

[P01] Jung Hee Cheon, <u>Jai Hyun Park</u>, Wootae Kim, "Apparatus for Processing Non-polynomial Operation on Homomorphic Encrypted Messages and Methods Thereof,"

• KOR 10-2304992, US 11757618, JPN 7449911, granted

PROJECTS

- "Data Protection in Virtual Environments (DPRIVE)". Supported by the *DARPA* Dec 2022 Sep 2023
- "A Study on Cryptographic Primitives for SNARK". Supported by the *IITP* Grant through the *Korean Government* Apr 2021 Aug 2024
- "Development and Library Implementation of Fully Homomorphic Machine Learning Algorithms supporting Neural Network Learning over Encrypted Data". Supported by the *IITP* Grant through the Korean Government
 Apr 2020 Dec 2023

EXPERIENCES

RESEARCH INTERN

CryptoLab Inc., Lyon, France

Jan 2024 – Mar 2024

CryptoLab Inc., Seoul, Korea

Jan 2023 – Feb 2023

MILITARY

Republic of Korea Army Discharged as a Sergeant Jul 2016 - Apr 2018

SERVICES

REVIEWER / EXTERNAL REVIEWER

- Design, Codes and Cryptography (DCC); Journal of Cryptology (JoC); Information Sciences; IEEE Access
- ANTS 2020; ASIACRYPT 2022, 2021; FHE.org 2022; PQCrypto 2023; EUROCRYPT 2023, 2024

[Last update: 2024-11-20]